(Penny:)I don't think so,
I'm clicking on
"One weird trick
for a flat belly,"
(Penny:)but I'm still seeing
"Celebrities who look like
their pets."
(Leonard:)Oh, I knew it,
(Leonard:)Sheldon changed the password.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Leonard:)Well, the new network name is,
"Ha ha ha, now I've got you,"
so...
(Leonard:)It's either Sheldon
or Gargamel from The Smurfs.
(Penny:)What a jerk.
You're good at revenge;
how do we get him back?
(Penny:)Well, my go-to move is usually
(Penny:)sleep with the
person's boyfriend,
(Penny:)but I kind of feel like
I'm already doing that.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I know what you did,
(Leonard:)now change the password back.
(Sheldon:)Well, powder me in sugar
and call me a donut,
(Sheldon:)if it isn't Leonard Hofstadter.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I'm warning you,
I can play this game, too.
(Sheldon:)If it's like
your 3-D chess game,
(Sheldon:)then you're out of your length,
width and depth.